

Worakamol Boonpriphan

My Contact

worakamol.rb@gmail.com

(+6686-516-7632

103/123 Moo 1 Bangkruai-Sainoi Rd., Bangkrang, Nonthaburi 11000

in http://linkedin.com/in/woraka mol-boonpriphan-b1898320a

Education Background

- Kasetsart University
 Bacheler's degree of Electrical Engineering
 Graduated in 2016, First Honor Class
- Udemy online platform
 - Active Listening Course
 - Difficult of Conversation Course
 - AUTOSAR Architecture
 - Diagnostic in AUTOSAR

Skill

 Embedded C Programming

Git

SVN

C Programming

C# Programming

MS office

Hobby

Photography Reading Blogger Model Maker

Language

English

Thai

About Me

I'm an Electrical Engineer captivated by Embedded System Development. With six years of experience, I love embracing new tech challenges. Additionally, I'm passionate about software development for ecofriendly solutions. Let's create a greener future together!

Work Experience

ThaiGerTec Co., Ltd. member of KPIT Technical Leader April 2023 – Present

Key responsibilities:

- Analyse the requirement and implement based on AUTOSAR standard
- · Support team in COM and DIAG stack.

ThaiGerTec Co., Ltd. member of KPIT Sr. software engineer, January 2022 – March 2023 Key responsibilities:

- Studied the AUTOSAR standard inn COMMUNICATION and DIAGNOSTIC stack to discussed with team
- Develop some simple features as per the requirement by using Davinci Tools

Silicon Craft Technology PLC

Sr. Embedded System Engineer March 2019 - December 2021 Key responsibilities:

- Analysed the requirement to develop the hardware/software prototype
- Expolred in a new fields of NFC technology and made a report
- Support customer on both software and hardware issue.

Silicon Craft Technology PLC

Embedded System Engineer August 2016 - March 2019

Key responsibilities:

- Implemented code based on the existing hardware due to the requirement
- Prepared test reports on each project to team.
- Designed some of simple hardware to be prototype.

Project

NFC Connect
Application

https://www.youtube.com/watch? v=KYy.gMaHrZOY

Action figure

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-

q7sew8rlxg

Light Timer Control

https://www.youtube.com/watch? v=56uli3fgygl&list=PLNVMfhpfdARu6Ef2 nM8FCofKmIA08uLL4&index=25